CONTACT

+66 54-1439-55

Atithiya.inthorn@gmail.com Bangkok 10800, Thailand linkedin.com/in/atithiya github.com/Atithiya

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap / Tailwind
- Javascript / React Js
- Node JS / Express JS
- MongoDB / SQL
- Git / Github
- Figma

SOFT SKILLS

- Growth mindset
- Persistence
- Responsibility
- Teamwork

LANGUAGE

- Thai (Native)
- English (TOEIC 790)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of laws (2017 - 2019) Ramkhamhaeng University

CERTIFICATED

- AML/CTPF: Anti-Money

 Laundering and Counter
 Terrorism and Proliferation of
 Weapon of Mass Destruction
 Financing Certified by the Anti-Money Laundering Office
 (Thailand)
- Junior Software Developer by Generation Thailand

LICENSE

Attorney At Law License

ATITHIYA INTHORN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a graduate of Generation JSD Boot Camp. Previously, I was in the document verification industry for 2 years. The experience allowed me to be oriented to detail and I'm willing to learn new technology. I am looking forward to applying my previous work experiences and newly developed technical skills to launch my career in a tech field.

EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Developer Cohort 5 July - October 2023 Generation Thailand

- Developed a workout tracking website with both desktop and mobile-responsive web designs using the MERN Stack, which includes MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, and Node.js.
- Acquired essential behavioral skills for both the workplace and personal life, including a growth mindset, effective communication, personal responsibility, and persistence.
- Developed multiple mini-projects using HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and React JS, including CRUD React JS projects.

Quality Control - Document Quality July 2022 - June 2023 PRTR Group Co.,Ltd.

Operating for ShopeeXpress (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

- Verified the employees' work to verify whether the delivery of the parcel complies with the process with oriented to detail skill.
- Verified procedure and privacy complied to the PDPA law by analyzing the submitted data.
- Applied problem-solving skills to handle clients who complaint over an employee's behavior.

KYC Officer April 2021 - June 2022 Workmate Solution Recruitment Co., Ltd. Operating for Bitkub Online Co., Ltd

- Verified the identity verification lists, In advance of creating a customer account.
- Investigated high-risk of client's occupation with curiosity, reported where necessary, and obtained all necessary documentation to complete the customer profile.
- Completed daily KPIs and was promoted to Data Cleansing position.

PROJECT

KeepFit (Workout application)

 Developed a workout tracking application geared towards elderly users, facilitating the logging of daily workouts and presenting a user-friendly dashboard.